http://www.ubbcentral.com/privacy.php

Privacy Policy
UBBCentral respects your privacy. That's why we have created this Privacy Statement to explain how and why we collect certain information online, and how we use that information. This statement also explains how you can prevent collection of certain information about yourself, if you choose. Please take a few moments to read our Privacy Statement. This statement applies to both information we collect from visitors to the ubbcentral.com Web site, as well as information we collect or have access to when we host bulletin and message boards for other websites.
Right to Change Policy
As UBBCentral is constantly innovating and enhancing the products and services it provides to its users, this Privacy Statement will also continue to change to match the products and services we make available. As such, we reserve the right to change this statement to match the products and services we provide. If we make any material change to this statement, we will change the date at the top of this statement to reflect the effective date of the change. When you visit our site or use our products and services, we encourage you to check the date of this Privacy Statement to ensure you are aware of any updates.
However, regardless of how this Privacy Statement may change or evolve over time, UBBCentral will not collect or maintain your private and personally identifiable information without your consent. Further, if you consent to give us your personal information, we will keep it confidential and will not sell, license or disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent, unless we are compelled to do so under the law or to comply with a court order.
Contact for Privacy Inquiries
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or other questions about privacy on the UBBCentral site, please contact:
Or Via E-mail: support@ubbcentral.com
Types of Information We Collect
Generally, you are free to browse the ubbcentral.com site without submitting any personal information. We do not collect any of your personal information (such as a name, address or e-mail address) when you visit the ubbcentral site, unless you download one of our products, register or have registered to use one of our products or services, complete one of our evaluations, or otherwise agree to submit to us such information. As part of such processes, you have the opportunity to decline further promotional materials or other notifications from us regarding special offers and information from UBBCentral. Types of information collected on specific services on the ubbcentral.com site are described in more detail below.
Registration on Our Site
UBBCentral requires users who want to participate in the ubbcentral.com support message boards to register. In order to register, you must provide us with a username (which does not have to be your real name), password and a valid e-mail address. This allows us to protect our community from abusive postings and provides a verifiable point of contact should legal questions arise. At any time, you have the ability to keep your e-mail address hidden from other users by selecting that option within your user profile.
When you register, you have the option of providing some additional information such as occupation, interests, and homepage URL. This optional information is made available to other bulletin or message board users to foster a sense of community. If you have any concerns about providing this information, simply leave the fields blank and your registration will still be processed.
IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE you are not allowed to participate in the ubbcentral support forums, or to provide any personal information on our site.
Newsletter Subscription
UBBCentral offers an option to subscribe to a periodic newsletter regarding our company's activities, promotions, product announcements and news items. The only piece of information required is the user's e-mail address, which is only used to distribute the requested newsletter. You can "unsubscribe" to the newsletter at any time by visiting our Newsletter page
Cookies
UBBCentral uses browser cookies to facilitate your experience with our products and services. These cookies are small sections of code that our server sends to your browser which it can then store on your hard drive. If you choose to accept these cookies, they enable us to recognize that your browser has previously visited and used our site, products or services and, based on your browser's previous visits, assist us with tailoring the information and content, banners and promotions you view. An example of the customization allowed by the use of such cookies is to retain your username and password as part of the UBBCentral forums on our site so you don't have to re-enter them each time you visit. These cookies do not collect, store or maintain your private, personally identifiable information. You do not have to accept these cookies to visit or use the UBBCentral site or our products and services, and you can choose to refuse our cookie, delete our cookie from your hard drive or turn off the UBBCentral cookie at any time by updating your user profile preferences.
Purchasing and/or Credit Card Information
UBBCentral strives to maintain strict security for your private information. Our online ordering pages are SSL enabled, providing a secure means of ordering our products. We do not maintain any credit card information at UBBCentral, which means that you have to provide it each time you make a purchase, but also means that your information is controlled by you alone.
Technical Support
Any personal information you provide to us in the course of obtaining technical support, or asking other questions about UBBCentral will be used only for the purposes for which it was submitted. We may store the information, but we will not use it for any other purposes or disclose it to any third parties.
Use and Disclosure of Your Information
UBBCentral uses the personal information it collects from forms you fill out on our site or in our product and service registrations to:
1. Allow users to access and use our products and services;
2. Supply users with installation instructions, download, access or use information, and technical support information;
3. Provide users of products and service on our site with information about special offers and promotions; and
4. Improve our products and services by using statistical analysis and evaluation of user data.
We use the anonymous information we collect from the other methods described above, such as cookie information, to collect broad demographic information about user trends, count the number of users of our products and services, to provide advertising services and to continue to enhance and improve our products and services.
We do not and will not disclose your private, personally identifiable information to any third party for any purpose without your prior consent. However, UBBCentral reserves the right to disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of our company, its employees, customers, or the public.
All reasonable care is taken by our staff in handling your personal information to ensure its security both offline and online. It is our policy to destroy server access and any personal information provided during the technical support process upon completion of the technical support incident.
Changing or Updating Personal Information
If you would like to update or change your user profile on our message boards, click here.
To update the information on your registered UBB license, click here.
If you have questions regarding your information, you can contact our Support at support@ubbcentral.com.
Postings on Message Boards
It is important for you to remain aware that when you provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number) in a posting on any message board, that information is available to any other person or user having access and use of that message board, and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason, we discourage you from offering any personally identifying information within a posting to any message board.
Forum Store
This site is protected by NetworkScanning.com providing Vulnerability Assessment testing and security services.
